widencollective.com 2012-06-10

# Privacy Statement | Widen Collective

## Privacy Statement

_Posted on:_ July 26th, 2011 _by_ dtempleton [No Comments](http://www.widencollective.com/privacy-statement/#respond "Comment on Privacy Statement")

### Privacy Policy

Widen Enterprises, Inc. is committed to the privacy of all users and has created this policy to disclose our privacy practices to ensure users are comfortable with sharing pertinent information. Widen Enterprises, Inc. pledges to maintain integrity and professional practices while working with private information.

#### Collecting Personal Information

Users will be required to register and share personal and company information when accessing certain areas of [www.widencollective.com](http://www.widencollective.com/). The individual will have access to information upon completing the required fields and may option out of receiving additional information from [www.widencollective.com](http://www.widencollective.com/). Email containing information may be generated by administrators to keep you informed as to the status of a request from [www.widencollective.com](http://www.widencollective.com/).

#### Child Information Protection

This site does not knowingly collect information from any children and is created for general user access only.

#### Tracking Information

Activity within the site will be captured for tracking and monitoring purposes. This information will be used to generate reports on usage and to determine popular areas of the [www.widencollective.com](http://www.widencollective.com/).

#### Questions

Questions about this privacy policy should be directed to Privacy Policy Associate at [info@widen.com](mailto:info@widen.com).
